questions = [
	{
		'topic': 'Journals, articles and books',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'What is the name of Australia\'s number one roller derby magazine?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/38391601'],
				'answer': 'Hit & Miss'
			},
			{
				'question': 'A week with ____ was the name of the proceedings in which a wildlife sanctuary is mentioned?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/30283740'],
				'answer': 'A week with elephants'
			},
			{
				'question': 'On the 10th page of results when you search for ferns in the books zone, what animal is part of a book title in those results?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/8620446'],
				'answer': 'Horse'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Who wrote an article about a cheese carving competition in 2007?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/127558107'],
				'answer': 'Lori Aratani'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Which book by Garth Nix is also available in braille?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/7285721'],
				'answer': 'Serena and the sea serpent'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What is the name of the cow that needed a haircut?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/169739287'],
				'answer': 'Hairy Hettie'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		'topic': 'Newspapers',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'Who shot Joseph Kentwell with a pea rifle?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/105127974'],
				'answer': 'His daughter'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Whose luck was dead out when he was caught selling wine without a license?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/120159722'],
				'answer': 'Emil Beuschel'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What did the PM abolish in 1941 in an effort to avoid expenditure on non-essential items?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/38326584'],
				'answer': 'Christmas cards'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What was the name of the postmaster for Temora in 1882?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/13510450', 'http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/144374386'],
				'answer': 'Mr William Weatherall'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What was the top most headline for the May 22 1947 issue of the Newcastle Morning Herald?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/140311464'],
				'answer': 'Thousands losing jobs in steel industry'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Where does Bessie Gwydir need to call to see her sister?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/5750465'],
				'answer': '212 Little Collins St East'
			}

		]
	},
	{	
		'topic': 'Pictures, photos, maps',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'What kitchen appliance is used as a letterbox in one of our photos from Flickr user, spelio?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/152909575'],
				'answer': 'Microwave'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What did Dr Schomburgk design in 1874?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/34052168', 'http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/34489720'],
				'answer': 'Adelaide Botanic Gardens'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What is the name of the unusual piece of evidence used in a Queensland murder trial?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/178528777'],
				'answer': 'Peter'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What Australian animal is depicted in the artwork by Master Jake?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/162329940'],
				'answer': 'Koala'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Which map is also a game that follows an air race from England to Australia?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/31245791'],
				'answer': 'Sir Ross Smith aeroplane race game'
			}
		],

	},
	{
		'topic': 'Music, videos',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'Which organisation holds Doolallynastics?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/27499549'],
				'answer': 'University of Melbourne Library'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What is the title of a documentary style film that combines a narrative about a roadie called Trip with a live concert performance by a heavy metal band?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/190083470'],
				'answer': 'Metallica: through the never'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What kind of technology can help track Antarctic blue whales according to one Radio National program?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/191716564'],
				'answer': 'Acoustic technology'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What is the title of a 29 minute film about New Zealand working dogs that is on VHS?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/17415766'],
				'answer': 'Dogstar'
			},
			{
				'question': 'How many libraries hold the 1995 album Frogstomp by Silverchair?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/21485747'],
				'answer': '24'
			}

		]
	},
	{
		'topic': 'People, archives, lists',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'How many resources are by the Australian Oilseeds Federation according to the people record in Trove?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/people/612129'],
				'answer': '42'	
			},
			{
				'question': 'Who did Billy Hughes inscribe a copy of The Splendid Adventure to?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/21866584'],
				'answer': 'Sir Reginald Wingate'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What type of farm did Dave De Hugard grow up on?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/people/514537'],
				'answer': 'Tobacco'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Which battalion was T. Murphy a part of when he wrote his war diary?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/33118302'],
				'answer': '5th battalion'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What type of sheep was George Earp interested in?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/people/1531828'],
				'answer': 'Dorset Horn sheep'
			}
		]
	},
	{
		'topic': 'Mixed bag',
		'questions': [
			{
				'question': 'Fill in the blanks. It was a Hospital ____ and ____ Day in Warrnambool on February 2 1916.',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/73868956'],
				'answer': 'Hospital Egg and Flower Day'
			},
			{
				'question': 'How many editions are there of The Complete Adventures of and Cuddlepie by May Gibbs?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/6486857'],
				'answer': '68'
			},
			{
				'question': 'How many sheets of sections are there in the atlas on Melbourne sewerage?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/32543258'],
				'answer': '14 sheets of sections'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Where was the wax voodoo doll found that was delivered to the Burleigh Police Station?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/work/178528782'],
				'answer': 'Wilpark Crest, Currumbin'
			},
			{
				'question': 'Who contributed the Kodak Limited record to Trove?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/people/894367'],
				'answer': 'Libraries Australia'
			},
			{
				'question': 'What is the tenth item on the list on Henry Kendall poetry?',
				'link': ['http://trove.nla.gov.au/ndp/del/article/60409379'],
				'answer': 'Song - Beauty\'s Eyes'
			},
		]
	}
]